

Carlos Hernández-Bueno Regojo

Software engineer and Cybersecurity specialist

WORK EXPERIENCE



FULL STACK DEVELOPER

iTrack Europe, Geopositioning company based in Salamanca February 2021 to August 2021 (6 meses)

 Development of a geopositioning platform

CYBERSECURITY EXPERT

Grupo MasMovil, Telecommunication company based in Madrid
October 2023 until Present

- Cybersecurity Assesment of our apps
- Work on the automation of Cloud Armor management with Terraform

EDUCATION



DEGREE IN COMPUTER ENGINEERING AND TECHNOLOGY BUSINESS ADMINISTRATION AND MANAGEMENT Institution: Universidad Pontificia de Salamanca

Year of graduation: 2021

DOUBLE MASTER IN COMPUTER SCIENCE AND CYBERSECURITY University: Universidad Madrid Carlos III

Currently studying

https://www.linkedin.com/in/carlos -hernandez-bueno-regojo/ carloshdez.bueno@gmail.com

+34 645 268 230

SUMMARY

I am a dynamic professional with a solid foundation in Computer Engineering and Technology Business Administration, complemented by ongoing studies in Computer Science and Cybersecurity. I bring practical experience due to the various activities I have developed in my life demonstrating adaptability and leadership through my roles, including volunteer positions coordinating IT efforts at an international level for BEST AISBL.

TRABAJO VOLUNTARIO Y AFICIONES

- Volunteer in BEST (09/2021 -Present)
 - Non-profit organization formed by technology students from all over Europe.
 - Treasurer of the XVIII Board of BEST Madrid Carlos III (2022-2023)
 - IT Department Coordinator for BEST AISBL. Managed the work on IT for the whole organization at an international level. (2023-2024)

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Javascript, C/C++, Java, Python, React, Node.js, DJango, Flask, PHP, MongoDB, MySQL, Terraform, GCP.
- Problem resolution, Change management
- Team work, Team dynamics, Team communication